<?xml version="1.0"?>
<interface>
    <summary>
        <osnametext lang="en">The Operating System you are running is: </osnametext>
        <os name="gnulinux">
            <summary lang="en">GNU/Linux is made up mostly of freedomware. However, many systems have several pieces of propreitary software installed (find out why this is bad).</summary>
            <distro name="debian">
                <summary lang="en">Debian has a good commitment to freedomware, but not quite as far as gnewsense.</summary>
            </distro>
            <distro name="ubuntu">
                <summary lang="en">Ubuntu has a good commitment to freedomware, but not as much as others such as fedora, debian and gnewsense.</summary>
            </distro>
            <distro name="gnewsense">
                <summary lang="en">gNewSense contains only freedomware, but it is possible that propreitary software may have been installed on it.</summary>
            </distro>
            <distro name="suse">
                <summary lang="en">SuSE has an okay commitment to freedomware, but has signed suspicous patent deals.</summary>
            </distro>
            <scantext lang="en">Click the scan button below to scan for propreitary software that is installed on your system.</scantext>
        </os>
        <os name="windows">
            <summary lang="en">Windows is a proprietary Operating System. However various pieces of freedomware can be installed.</summary>
            <scantext lang="en">Click scan to find common pieces of free software, then our wizard will help you start using more.</scantext>
            <migrationtext>We can also help you install a free software Operating System, such as Ubuntu.</migrationtext>
        </os>
    </summary>
    <reasons>
        <reason name="full" lang="en">Piece of propreiary software</reason>
    </reasons>
    <errors>
        <noscan>Unfortunately the scan functionality does not work for this GNU/Linux distriubtion yet. Please contact us so that we can add it.</noscan>
        <othunix>Unix based, but not GNU/Linux.
Unfortunately we do not support this operating system yet. If you would like to help us, please tell us what system you are using.</othunix>
    </errors>
</interface>
